{"choices":[{"subContentId":"612d067b-eb47-4480-9e0d-21af8e0ff045","question":"<p>How many languages are you able to recognise. Guess them! If you don't know, maybe MT could help you. Try guessing the language for the various translations of the English sentence \"X\" below. If you want, you can use an MT system to make a more informed decision. Good luck!<\/p>\n\n<p>GUESS THE LANGUAGE (only one is correct). Following there is the translation of the following English sentence \"Articles 5 to 7 of this Directive do not apply to containers for gases which are compressed, liquefied or dissolved under pressure.\"<\/p>\n\n<p>Good luck!<\/p>\n\n<p>First sentence:&nbsp;<\/p>\n\n<p>Artyku\u0142 5-7 niniejszej dyrektywy nie stosuje si\u0119 do zbiornik\u00f3w lub pojemnik\u00f3w zawieraj\u0105cych gazy spr\u0119\u017cone, skroplone lub rozpuszczone pod ci\u015bnieniem.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Polish<\/p>\n","<p>Romanian<\/p>\n","<p>Danish<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"60ff1a0d-b2be-4f93-acae-88c66a6bbe89","question":"<p class=\"MsoPlainText\">Os artigos 5\u00ba., 6\u00ba. e 7\u00ba. da presente directiva n\u00e3o s\u00e3o aplic\u00e1veis aos recipientes que cont\u00eam gases comprimidos, liquefeitos e dissolvidos sob press\u00e3o.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Portuguese<\/p>\n","<p>German<\/p>\n","<p>Maltese<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"a4acbf9c-4997-49c1-8568-7645dccf8c46","question":"<p class=\"MsoPlainText\">Artiklerne 5-7 i dette direktiv finder ikke anvendelse p\u00e5 beholdere , der indeholder komprimerede , flydende eller under tryk opl\u00f8ste gasser<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Danish<\/p>\n","<p>Estonian<\/p>\n","<p>Swedish<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"ad25752e-54c1-4b26-b1a7-3239fcc8178f","question":"<p>\u03a4\u03b1 \u03ac\u03c1\u03b8\u03c1\u03b1 5 \u03ad\u03c9\u03c2 7 \u03c4\u03b7\u03c2 \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03bf\u03cd\u03c3\u03b7\u03c2 \u03bf\u03b4\u03b7\u03b3\u03af\u03b1\u03c2 \u03b4\u03b5\u03bd \u03ad\u03c7\u03bf\u03c5\u03bd \u03b5\u03c6\u03b1\u03c1\u03bc\u03bf\u03b3\u03ae \u03b5\u03c0\u03af \u03b4\u03bf\u03c7\u03b5\u03af\u03c9\u03bd \u03c0\u03bf\u03c5 \u03c0\u03b5\u03c1\u03b9\u03ad\u03c7\u03bf\u03c5\u03bd \u03b1\u03ad\u03c1\u03b9\u03b1 \u03c3\u03c5\u03bc\u03c0\u03b9\u03b5\u03c3\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03b1 , \u03c5\u03b3\u03c1\u03bf\u03c0\u03bf\u03b9\u03b7\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03b1 \u03ae \u03b4\u03b9\u03b1\u03bb\u03b5\u03bb\u03c5\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03b1 \u03c5\u03c0\u03cc \u03c0\u03af\u03b5\u03c3\u03b7<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Greek<\/p>\n","<p>Slovene<\/p>\n","<p>Bulgarian<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"0457fa7f-38a6-4126-8387-bbe4cdc13f06","question":"<p>K\u00e4esoleva direktiivi artikleid 5-7 ei kohaldata mahutitele, mis on t\u00e4idetud suru-, vedel- v\u00f5i r\u00f5hu all lahustatud gaasiga.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Estonian<\/p>\n","<p>Latvian<\/p>\n","<p>Lithuanian<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"cfb5c5ea-f33e-4a98-b0bc-c6976da303d3","question":"<p>\u0160ios direktyvos 5-7 straipsniai netaikomi susl\u0117gt\u0173, suskystint\u0173 ar auk\u0161tame sl\u0117gyje i\u0161tirpint\u0173 duj\u0173 konteineriams.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Lithuanian<\/p>\n","<p>Latvian<\/p>\n","<p>Estonian<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"44b17e4c-6217-4d5c-a0eb-5cf54cb0afcf","question":"<p class=\"MsoPlainText\">\u0160\u012bs direkt\u012bvas 5. l\u012bdz 7. pantu nepiem\u0113ro tvertn\u0113m saspiestai, sa\u0161\u0137idrin\u0101tai vai zem spiediena iz\u0161\u0137\u012bdin\u0101tai g\u0101zei.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Latvian<\/p>\n","<p>Finnish<\/p>\n","<p>Slovak<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"f58773f1-6492-4011-8b68-32622ce92cd8","question":"<p class=\"MsoPlainText\">\u010cl\u00e1nky 5 a\u017e 7 tejto smernice neplatia pre n\u00e1dr\u017ee na plyn, ktor\u00fd je stla\u010den\u00fd, skvapalnen\u00fd alebo rozpusten\u00fd pod tlakom.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Slovak<\/p>\n","<p>Spanish<\/p>\n","<p>Croatian<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"a6010318-cbbe-4b6f-b06c-aa40b0a6b41b","question":"<p class=\"MsoPlainText\">T\u00e4m\u00e4n direktiivin 5-7 artiklaa ei sovelleta s\u00e4ili\u00f6ihin, jotka sis\u00e4lt\u00e4v\u00e4t puristettua, nesteytetty\u00e4 tai paineen alla liuotettua kaasua<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Finnish<\/p>\n","<p>Dutch<\/p>\n","<p>French<\/p>\n"]},{"subContentId":"4ea4966e-31f9-44aa-8cc1-0d19fd4383c9","question":"<p class=\"MsoPlainText\">\u010clena 5 in 7 te direktive se ne uporabljata za posode za plin, ki je stisnjen, uteko\u010dinjen ali raztopljen pod pritiskom.<\/p>\n","answers":["<p>Slovene<\/p>\n","<p>Czech<\/p>\n","<p>Irish<\/p>\n"]}],"overallFeedback":[{"from":0,"to":33,"feedback":"Try again!"},{"from":34,"to":66,"feedback":"Not bad!"},{"from":67,"to":100,"feedback":"Great score!"}],"behaviour":{"autoContinue":true,"timeoutCorrect":2000,"timeoutWrong":3000,"soundEffectsEnabled":true,"enableRetry":true,"enableSolutionsButton":true,"passPercentage":100},"l10n":{"nextButtonLabel":"Next question","showSolutionButtonLabel":"Show solution","retryButtonLabel":"Retry","solutionViewTitle":"Solution list","correctText":"Correct!","incorrectText":"Incorrect!","muteButtonLabel":"Mute feedback sound","closeButtonLabel":"Close","slideOfTotal":"Slide :num of :total","scoreBarLabel":"You got :num out of :total points","solutionListQuestionNumber":"Question :num","a11yShowSolution":"Show the solution. The task will be marked with its correct solution.","a11yRetry":"Retry the task. Reset all responses and start the task over again."}}